<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">


<tv source-info-name="">
 <channel id="0-0-2804-127.0.0.1-50001">
  <display-name></display-name>
 </channel>

 <programme start="20101003100000 +0400" stop="20101003120000 +0400" channel="0-0-2804-127.0.0.1-50001">
  <title> <![CDATA[Dark Descent]]> </title>
   <desc lang="en">Deep in the Mariana Sea Basin, several miners have died under mysterious circumstances. Officer Will Murdock (Dean Cain) of the Deep Submersible Division is brought down to investigate. He soon uncovers a conspiracy which could prevent him from ever reaching the surface of the ocean alive.</desc>
 </programme>
 <programme start="20101003120000 +0400" stop="20101003140000 +0400" channel="0-0-2804-127.0.0.1-50001">
  <title> <![CDATA[The Matrix]]> </title>
   <desc lang="en">The film describes a future in which reality perceived by humans is actually the Matrix, a simulated reality created by sentient machines in order to pacify and subdue the human population while their bodies' heat and electrical activity are used as an energy source.</desc>
 </programme>
 <programme start="20101003140000 +0400" stop="20101003160000 +0400" channel="0-0-2804-127.0.0.1-50001">
  <title> <![CDATA[THE MATRIX RELOADED]]> </title>
   <desc lang="en">Neo and the rebel leaders estimate that they have 72 hours until 250,000 probes discover Zion and destroy it and its inhabitants. During this, Neo must decide how he can save Trinity from a dark fate in his dreams.</desc>
 </programme>
 <programme start="20101003160000 +0400" stop="20101003180000 +0400" channel="0-0-2804-127.0.0.1-50001">
  <title> <![CDATA[THE MATRIX REVOLUTIONS]]> </title>
   <desc lang="en">Everything that has a beginning has an end. The human city of Zion defends itself against the massive invasion of the machines as Neo fights to end the war at another end. Martial Arts-Keanu Reeves</desc>
 </programme>
 <programme start="20101003180000 +0400" stop="20101003200000 +0400" channel="0-0-2804-127.0.0.1-50001">
  <title> <![CDATA[The Deal]]> </title>
   <desc lang="en">A Wall Street financial hot shot and his eager new recruit get involved in government secrecy, illegal oil trading and the Russian Mafia. Starting:Christian Slater and Selma Blair.</desc>
 </programme>
 <programme start="20101003200000 +0400" stop="20101003220000 +0400" channel="0-0-2804-127.0.0.1-50001">
  <title> <![CDATA[The Valet]]> </title>
   <desc lang="en">François, a car service valet at a top Paris hotel, is caught by a paparazzo's camera in a picture with business tycoon Pierre Levasseur and his mistress, Elena. In order to save his reputation, his marriage, and his affair, the resourceful Levasseur looks to control the story by setting up François and Elena as a pretend couple, faking out the tabloids and his wife in the process.</desc>
 </programme>
 <programme start="20101003220000 +0400" stop="20101004000000 +0400" channel="0-0-2804-127.0.0.1-50001">
  <title> <![CDATA[OUT OF SIGHT]]> </title>
   <desc lang="en">A bank robber breaks out of jail and shares a moment of mutual attraction with a US Marshall he has taken as a hostage.</desc>
 </programme>
 <programme start="20101004000000 +0400" stop="20101004020000 +0400" channel="0-0-2804-127.0.0.1-50001">
  <title> <![CDATA[The Skeleton Key]]> </title>
   <desc lang="en">A young woman discovers a terrible secret while caring for an elderly man in this supernatural thriller. Caroline (Kate Hudson) is a care provider for the aged who is hired away from the hospice where she works by Violet Devereaux (Gena Rowlands). Violet needs someone to help take care of her husband, Ben (John Hurt), who is in poor health and doesn't have long to live. . It isn't long before Caroline discovers evidence that suggests Ben and Violet are members of a sinister voodoo cult, and that ghosts walk in the Devereaux mansion. stars Peter Sarsgaard and Joy Bryant-2005</desc>
 </programme>
 <programme start="20101004020000 +0400" stop="20101004040000 +0400" channel="0-0-2804-127.0.0.1-50001">
  <title> <![CDATA[Bookies]]> </title>
   <desc lang="en">Centers on four college friends who become small-time bookies, only to find their world spinning dangerously out of control when their greed attracts the attention of organized crime.</desc>
 </programme>
 <programme start="20101004040000 +0400" stop="20101004053000 +0400" channel="0-0-2804-127.0.0.1-50001">
  <title> <![CDATA[A Real Friend]]> </title>
   <desc lang="en">Estrella (Nerea Inchausti), A lonely girl who loves horror books and Lives with her widow mother Angela (Goya Toledo). Angela has an unresolved trauma after she got raped in the past. Estrella invites her friend Vampiro to dinner, and when Angela sees her daughter's friend, she feels scary, haunted by her past.</desc>
 </programme>
 <programme start="20101004053000 +0400" stop="20101004070000 +0400" channel="0-0-2804-127.0.0.1-50001">
  <title> <![CDATA[Bookies]]> </title>
   <desc lang="en">Centers on four college friends who become small-time bookies, only to find their world spinning dangerously out of control when their greed attracts the attention of organized crime.</desc>
 </programme>
 <programme start="20101004070000 +0400" stop="20101004083000 +0400" channel="0-0-2804-127.0.0.1-50001">
  <title> <![CDATA[OUT OF SIGHT]]> </title>
   <desc lang="en">A bank robber breaks out of jail and shares a moment of mutual attraction with a US Marshall he has taken as a hostage.</desc>
 </programme>
 <programme start="20101004083000 +0400" stop="20101004100000 +0400" channel="0-0-2804-127.0.0.1-50001">
  <title> <![CDATA[The Road Killers]]> </title>
   <desc lang="en">When a man and his family take a road trip on their vacation they are confronted by a psychotic motorist who terrorizes them on the lonely stretch of highway. Starting:Christopher Lambert, Craig Sheffer.</desc>
 </programme>
 <programme start="20101004100000 +0400" stop="20101004150000 +0400" channel="0-0-2804-127.0.0.1-50001">
  <title> <![CDATA[The Deal]]> </title>
   <desc lang="en">A Wall Street financial hot shot and his eager new recruit get involved in government secrecy, illegal oil trading and the Russian Mafia. Starting:Christian Slater and Selma Blair.</desc>
 </programme>
 <programme start="20101004150000 +0400" stop="20101004160000 +0400" channel="0-0-2804-127.0.0.1-50001">
  <title> <![CDATA[The Valet]]> </title>
   <desc lang="en">François, a car service valet at a top Paris hotel, is caught by a paparazzo's camera in a picture with business tycoon Pierre Levasseur and his mistress, Elena. In order to save his reputation, his marriage, and his affair, the resourceful Levasseur looks to control the story by setting up François and Elena as a pretend couple, faking out the tabloids and his wife in the process.</desc>
 </programme>
 <programme start="20101004160000 +0400" stop="20101004180000 +0400" channel="0-0-2804-127.0.0.1-50001">
  <title> <![CDATA[Ariana's Quest]]> </title>
   <desc lang="en">A princess who has been robbed of her kingdom learns the secret that had before kept it safe from harm. Now she must change time itself in order to regain her land and free her people.</desc>
 </programme>
</tv>
